Taylor, Mildred Frick; Papers apap280
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New York State History, 1940-1970; 4.2 cubic ft.
  - "New York Historical Society to Hear About Old DeBary Days", Undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - New York Landmarks, 1957 January (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - New York Meeting, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - New York State Preservation Plan, 1970 August 20 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - New York State's Year of History Poem Freedoms Dream, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - New York Trade on the Great Lakes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - News Clippings - Erie Canal Museum - Fort Hunter, 1955-1957; Undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - News Release - "Year of History", 1958; 1960 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Newsletter - East Fishkill Historical Society, 1961 December (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Newsletter - Geneva Historical Society, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Newsletter - Ontario Historical Society, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Niagara Frontier, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Nomination - Marian P. Croake and Edith Stevenson, 1970 April (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Northeast Stonehouse Reconstruction, 1970 September (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - The Northern Traveller, Undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - NY Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - NYS Association of Museum, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - NYS Council on the Arts, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - NYS Historic Trust - Bill to Authorize Municipalities to Acquire Property for Historic Sites, 1969 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - NYS Historic Trust Capital Construction, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1967 August 22 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1967 November 28 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 May 28 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 July 23 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 August 27 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 October 9 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1968 December 11 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 August 26 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 October 28 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 October 28 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1969 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 February (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 April 28 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 May 19 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - NYS Historic Trust Meeting, 1970 July-August (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - NYS Historical Association Calendar, 1963 January -March (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - NYS Historical Association - Cooperstown, NY, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - NYS Historical Association - Seminars on American Culture, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - NYS Historical Interpretation Program, 1967 May (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - NYS Historic Trust - Legislative Program - Conservation Law, 1969 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Odell Tavern - Irvington, NY, 1968 February (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Ogden L. Mills, 1969 October (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Old Bergen Art Guild, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Old Bethpage Village Restoration, 1968 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Old Bethpage Village Restoration - Nassau County, 1968 February (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Onondaga Historical Association, 1957 November (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Otto E. Koegel - Resume, 1970; Undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Outdoor Program, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Ottawa Historical Society, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Park Commission Bill - Erie Canal, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Parrott Hall - NYS - Agriculture Experiment Station Geneva, NY, 1968 June (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Parrott Hall Supplement Report, Undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Parrott's Famed Cannon Perfected and Produced at Cold Spring Foundry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Partridge Place, 1958 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission, 1942; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania History in Outline, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Pennsbury Manor - Americana Forum, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Perinton Historical Society, 1959 January 7 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Perrines Bridge, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Personnel Policy Program - Fourth Revision, 1968 August 21 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pills, Plaster, and Phlebotomy, ca. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "A Pleasant Land to Tread Upon", 1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pleasure Boating Handbook, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Points of Interests near the Erie Canal Museum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Policy Statement, 1968 July 23 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Policy Statement, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Position Paper, 1967 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Preservation of Historic Districts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Preservation of Historic Properties, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Preserving our Past - An Investment in our Future, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases on Historic Sites, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Proposal for Commemorating the War of 1812, 1968 July (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Proposal for the Creation of a Distinguished Professorship Exchange for Canadian-United States Relations, 1970 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Proposal - Louis L. Tucker, 1968 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Proposals for a NYS Canal Museum and Lock Restoration Project, 1955; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Proposed Capital Construction Requests, 1967 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Proposed Constitution for National Council of State Historic Preservation Liaison Officers, 1969 September 5 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Proposed Rehabilitation Program for Schuyler Mansion, 1967 May 8 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Proposed State Historic Sites, 1967 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Publications of the American Association for State and Local History, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Putnam County Historical Society, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Reappointment of Emma Sneed, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - A Recommended Checklist for Evaluating Historic Sites Proposals: A Report to the NYS Historic Trust, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Re-issue History of Delaware County - Henry Graham Ashmead, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Report on the Action Civil Polytechnic Institute, 1969 October (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Report on Brykill Estate, 1970 September (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Report - Colonial Homestead, 1968 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Report - Commandant's House - New York Navy Yard, Brooklyn, 1968 June (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Report to the Committee on Park Commission, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Report - Elbert Hubbard and Roycroft - East Aurora, NY, 1967 July (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Report - Fort Delaware - Narrowsburg, NY, 1967 March-1968 Mach (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Report Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites - Recommendation, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - A Report on the L.M Hoyt Estate - Staatsburg, Duchess County, NY, 1969 October (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Report of the Meeting of the Commission to Commemorate the War of 1812 and the Composition of the Star Spangled Banner, 1967 December 8 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - A Report on Music Hall Remsen and Oneida Streets - Albany, 1969 August (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Report - New Windsor Cantonment, 1967 August (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Report - Newton Battlefield, 1968 April (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - A Report on the Ogden L. Mils Estate, 1969 October (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Report - Old Onaquaga Broome County, NY, 1968 June (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Report Requests Historic Sites, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Report to Rockefeller, 1968 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Report - Schuylerville Forts, 1968 January (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - A Report on the Stone Arch Bridge State Routes 52 and 52A - Sullivan, NY, 1969 August (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Reports - Visits to Bennington Battlefield, Saratoga Battle Monument, Grant Cottage and John Brown Far, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Requests For Legislative Committee Report, 1958-1959; Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Resolution for Submission, 1969 August 26 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Resumes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Richmontown Restoration, 1968 March (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Robert G. Ingersoll Birthplace, 1968 November (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Rochester, Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Rochester Museum Tour for Young People, 1952 August 12; 1956 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - "Rochester, Syracuse, and Eastern", Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rock Hall - Town of Hempstead Museum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Rome, 1968 August (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Rose Garden, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Rotary Club - Resolution, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Sackets Harbor, NY, 1969; Undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Saint Lawrence Seaway and the Future, Dr. Marvin A. Rapp, 1958 August 22 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Saint Paul's Church - Eastchester, 1940; 1958; Undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Salisbury House - Inspection, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Salvage Archeology; Some Basic Thoughts, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Saratoga Surrender Sites - Schuylerville, Saratoga County, 1968 February (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Saugus Iron Works Restoration, Undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Schuyler Mansion - National Historic Landmark, 1968 January 17 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Seminars on American Culture - Conservation of Museum Materials, 1960; Undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Seneca Falls Historical Society Museum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Shelburne Museum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Showboat - Brockport, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Site Evaluation Report Summary, Undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Sites Now Owned and Maintained by the State, Undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - "So you want a Good Museum" - A Guide to the Management of Small Museums, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Sodus Bay Yacht Club, Undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Sons of the Revolution in the State of NY, Undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - South Quaker Hill - F.J Hoyer, 1958; 1960; Undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - South Street Seaport, Undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Southhold Historical Society, Undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - A Special Exhibition of Oil Painting: "County Court Houses of NYS", 1958 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Statement - Making Historic Sites an Obligation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Steepletop - Austerlitz, New York, 1968 July (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Stony Brook Brochures, Undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Stony Point - Rockland County, NY, 1968 May (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Study Tour - Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites, 1957 October 30 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Suffolk Museum, 1962; Undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Suggested Bill - Bi-Centennial Commission, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Summary of Comments about the Central Business District of Troy, NY, 1970 April (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Summary Report on Archeology for 1969, 1970 January (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Supplementary Evaluation and Proposal for Development of Crown Point, NY, 1967 July (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Survey Consultants, Undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Survey of Historic Sites and Structures in Kansas, 1957 March (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Susan B. Anthony Memorial - Rochester, NY, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Taylor Retirement - T.E R.A Record Requests, Undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Thank Yous - Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Theodore E. Day - NYS Historical Trust Laws, 1967 December 19 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Association, 1958; Undated (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Centennial Celebration, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Touraide - Thruway Broadcasting System, Undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Trust Resolutions, 1968 February 26 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Tyron Place, Undated (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Union Station, 1967 December (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - U.S. Bond Brand - Expenses for Historical Societies, 1956; 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Van Deusen House and the Historic District of Hurley, 1968 April (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - VanLoon - Old Stone House, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Van Wyck - Jay House, 1967 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Vermont Historic Sites Commission, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Walking Tour - Brooklyn Heights, 1957 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Walking Tour - Madison Square - Gramercy Park Stuyvesant Square, 1956 April 8 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Walking Tour - Tour of Art, 1957 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Walking Tour - Wall Street to Battery, 1956 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Warren County - Restoration of Courthouse Costs, 1967 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Washington Hall - Endwell, Broome County, 1968 January (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Washington Park - Albany, NY, 1968 January (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County (1 of 3), 1960; 1962-1966; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Wayne County (2 of 3), 1960; 1962-1966; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wayne County (3 of 3), 1960; 1962-1966; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Weighlock Building - Correspondence, 1957-1959; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Wells Fargo Express, 1957 October 24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - West Point Foundry - Cold Springs, Putnam County, 1968 May (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Wilcox Mansion, 1966; 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Willets House, 1969 March (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Womans Union Building, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Yorkers - Junior Historians, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)